skylanders.com 2016-06-18

# Activision | Privacy Policy

**Activision uses "Cookies" to tailor content, marketing, and improve and adjust user experience. To find out more about "Cookies", and options available to manage them, pleaseclick here** **. By using this Activision online property, you consent to our use of "Cookies".**

**Welcome to Activision's Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy was last updated on January 25, 2016.**

Every day, millions of people worldwide use and enjoy Activision websites, products and services. We appreciate your trust in our products and services. In order to provide you with great games and make them better, Activision may collect both personal information and non-personal information (collectively, "Information"). We take care of how your Information is processed and used.

This Privacy Policy:

  * explains how Activision collects, stores, uses, and may transfer or disclose your **Information;**
  * applies to all Activision websites, products and services (" **Properties** ") **.**

Activision reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a modified version online at <https://www.activision.com/legal/privacy-policy>, so please review it frequently to ensure you are aware of any changes. If Activision makes a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will provide notice to you in our Privacy Policy as posted and on our home page.

**Table of Contents**

  * **1\. Summary and Scope of Activision Privacy Policy**
  * **2\. ESRB Certified Program**
  * **3\. Information We Collect and How We Use It**
  * **4\. Children and Parents**
  * **5\. Your Choices**
  * **6\. Sharing Information**
  * **7\. Security**
  * **8\. Accessing Information**
  * **9\. Contacting Us**
  * **10\. Important Notice**
  * **11\. California Privacy Rights**
  * **12\. Disclosure to Users Outside the US**
  * **13\. Cookie Policy**

**1\. Summary and Scope of Activision Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies to all Properties, including:

  * Activision websites, online products and services;
  * Activision console games; and
  * Activision mobile applications.

Whenever you use a Property we may collect, process, and combine Information; contact you from time to time; and provide you with customer service and other services you have requested. We may, from time to time, also disclose Information to Activision group companies, and/or share Information with suppliers and partners, in order to provide you with goods or services you have requested or online advertising selected by us.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to third party websites or online properties to which our Properties may link, and you accept Activision is not responsible for the security or privacy practices of any such third party websites or properties.

This Privacy Policy does not cover Information provided when you apply for a job at Activision. Please refer [here](https://www.activision.com/legal/applicant-privacy-policy) for more information.

**2\. ESRB  Privacy Certified Program**  
This Privacy Policy and the ESRB certification seals shown on our websites confirm that Activision is a licensee and participating member in the [Entertainment Software Rating Board's (" **ESRB** ") Privacy Certified Program](http://www.esrb.org/privacy/faq.jsp). To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative and ESRB Privacy Certified has reviewed and certified that we meet established online information collection and use practices on all Activision Properties where this Privacy Policy is posted.

Click here for details Hide details

As part of the ESRB Privacy Certified Program, we are subject to frequent audits of our websites and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by the ESRB.

Whenever you visit a website that displays the ESRB Privacy Certified certification seal, you may request information about:

  * Whether a company uses cookies, tracks IP Addresses or uses other passive means to collect information;
  * Who, if anyone, is collecting your personal information and how will it be used;
  * With whom, if anyone, will your personal information be shared;
  * What choices you have with regard to the use of your personal information;
  * How you can access and, if necessary, change the personal information a company collects and maintains;
  * Whether and how information is collected from children under 13;
  * How a company ensures data security, quality, and integrity;
  * Where and how to ask questions or file complaints.

_DISCLAIMER: Although ESRB Privacy Certified does not monitor non-English Activision Properties, Activision makes all best efforts to ensure that non-English Properties adhere to applicable data collection guidance and principles set forth by ESRB Privacy Certified, including adherence to the EU Directive._

If you believe that we have not responded to your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact the ESRB at:

_http://www.esrb.org/privacy/contact.jsp_

ESRB  
Attn: Privacy Certified Program  
420 Lexington Ave, Suite 2024  
New York, NY 10170  
_privacy@esrb.org_

Back to top

**3\. Information We Collect and How We Use It**

Activision may collect Information from you and other sources. We use and may combine that Information to operate, tailor content, personalize, adjust and improve our Properties, and to send you messages or personalized information about our games, your scores, new features and more, including for marketing and promotional purposes.

Click here for details Hide details

**Information Provided By You**  
Activision may collect Information from you when you: (A) create an Activision account with a Property; (B) use our Properties; (C) participate in sweepstakes, contests and promotions; (D) use Activision customer service; (E) choose to receive newsletters on products and services, receive marketing emails, and/or participate in surveys; (F) buy Activision services or products online; (G) use “send-a-friend” functionality; or (H) allow sharing through Social Media.

A. Creation of an Activision Account

Activision collects certain personal information from you when you register with a Property, such as your first and last name, address, postal code, email address and Activision user name. Additionally, we collect your date of birth and marketing preferences. With an Activision account you may enjoy a tailored service and support across the Properties such as the community portals, email newsletters and the games you love and enjoy.

Unfortunately, as of September 1st, 2015, we no longer offer Activision accounts to Russian based consumers.

B. Use of our Properties

When you visit or use our Properties we may collect, process and/or combine Information about your use of those Properties, such as websites you visited before and after you used a Property, browser type and language, IP address, hardware and software information, gameplay data, purchase histories, and Social Media data. We may use Cookies, trackers or similar technologies to do this. In addition, we or our partners may also use Cookies, trackers or similar technologies to serve ads in our Properties. Please see the Cookie Policy below for more details.

Activision may collect, process, and combine data such as your age, gender, interests, name, email address, gameplay, marketing preferences, customer service, and device-related information.

To provide fair gaming experience to all players, Activision uses anti-fraud technologies to prevent any cheating in our games.

C. Sweepstakes, Contests, and Promotions

When Activision runs contests or promotions on our Properties, we may collect certain Information from participants such as their name, address, postal code, email address, phone number, age and/or date of birth. That Information may be combined with other account information and will be used and shared in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

D. Interact with Customer Service

In order to provide you with customer service and assist you with resolving any issues you may have, Activision may collect personal information from you including your contact details, together with details of your customer service issue and its resolution.

E. Receive newsletters on products and services, receive marketing emails, and/or surveys

Activision may offer you the ability to receive newsletters periodically by email about our products and services. At any time, you can manage your preferences from your account settings and stop receiving further newsletters by unsubscribing from the link in the footer of each email we send to you.

We may, from time to time, send you surveys in order to improve player experience with our games.

F. Buy Activision products or services online

Activision does not collect any credit card and/or billing information when you purchase products or services (such as digital content) online. However, you may be required to provide credit card and/or billing information to one of our third-party vendors in order to complete a purchase. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of our third-party vendors before providing them with your personal information, as their privacy practices may vary from ours. At the time of purchase, you may also have the option to provide Information (such as your email address) to Activision for the purpose of sending you additional information or offers.

G. Send-a-Friend

From time to time, Activision may offer you the ability to email or message friends or family by using our "send-a-friend" tool. In the event we offer you this ability, we delete both sender and recipient email addresses after sending the message and only use the information we collect for the purpose of sending the email or message (unless we have separately collected the sender or recipient's details for other purposes described in this Privacy Policy). In using our "send-a-friend" tool, you confirm that you and the recipient know each other and that you have their consent to send them an email.

H. Social Media

You can interact with some Properties through social networking sites, such as Facebook and Twitter (or social media plug-ins and applications) ("Social Media"). When you interact with Activision and/or the Properties through Social Media you acknowledge that we may access your Information, solely in accordance with your Social Media privacy settings, and use it to (1) give you exclusive content; (2) personalize your online experience with us within and outside our Properties; and (3) contact you in accordance with applicable marketing preferences through Social Media or directly by sending you the latest news, special offerings, and rewards.

When you post personal information publicly through the Properties, or on Social Media, it may be viewable by other users of these sites and we cannot prevent further use of the personal information by third parties. For more information about how your Social Media uses and protects your personal information, please refer to their privacy policies and terms of use.

**Information Provided By Other Sources**  
We may also obtain Information about you from other sources, such as Social Media, our vendors, partners, and network advertising companies, and combine that Information with Information we have collected from or about you. We only collect Information from other sources where they have confirmed to us they are legally entitled to share it with us.

Back to top

**4\. Children and Parents**

Activision does not knowingly collect or store any personal information from children under 13.

We recognize a special need to protect the personal information of children. We urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses, phone numbers, or other personal information without parental permission, when online. Activision also recommends that parents familiarize themselves with parental controls available on consoles, mobile telephones, tablets and other devices they provide to their child and accompany their child if aged under 13 years of age when online. Parents should contact Activision immediately if they have any concerns. Please see the Contacting Us section below for further details.

Back to top

**5\. Your Choices**

You have choices over the Information provided by you and by other sources, and how that Information is used by Activision. You can exercise your choices by updating your preferences at any time and also by managing your settings on your devices and third party accounts.

Click here for details Hide details

**Your Choices about Information Provided By You:**

If you do not want to provide Activision with personal information then you can choose not to provide it. Please note that if you choose not to provide us with personal information, we may not be able to provide you with the relevant Activision product or service that you want. For example, without providing personal information, you will not be able to use the Properties and/or create an Activision account.

Your Choices about Information Provided by Third Parties:

You may be able to control how third parties collect and share your Information by changing your preferences or opting out of collection directly with those third parties. Before disclosing Information to third parties, we recommend you check their respective privacy policies for further details.

Your Choices About Activision Using Your Information:

You can exercise choices over how Activision uses your personal information and update your preferences at any time:

  * to remove yourself from individual contests or promotions, or from receiving email marketing or newsletters from Activision, simply click the unsubscribe link in the email or access your account from  _<https://www.activision.com/>_  and edit your email marketing preferences. You will need your password to access your account;
  * to disable selected Cookies from collecting information relating to the effectiveness of advertising campaigns or analytics data and from serving you with personalized advertising on our Properties or third party properties please see our Cookie Policy below.

If you opt-out of receiving email marketing communications from us, please note we may still contact you occasionally about the status of your account, such as to inform you that your account may be expiring, or for other service related information.

Back to top

**6\. Sharing Information**

Activision shares Information with

  * with the various Activision group companies for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy;
  * with vendors and partners engaged by Activision in order to provide you with goods or services you have requested or online advertising selected by us;
  * if required to do so by applicable law or regulation;
  * if necessary to exercise, establish or defend our legal rights;
  * if necessary to protect the vital interests of any person; and
  * in connection with the sale of our business or assets.

Please note that any information, including personal information that you reveal in a bulletin board, message board, chat room or other public forum is publicly viewable.

Click here for details Hide details

**Vendors**  
Vendors provide goods and services (for example, billing, consumer services support, consultancy, information technology hardware and software) to Activision in order to support, operate and develop the Properties and to deliver marketing communications on our behalf. We do not share Information with vendors to use for their own direct marketing purposes or any other purpose without your consent.

**Third Parties**  
Other third parties may need your Information in order to provide goods and/or services you have requested, for example, to deliver Activision digital content you have purchased through your games console, mobile phone, or tablet.

**Law**  
We may disclose your Information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, including but not limited to disclosure to law enforcement or other government officials in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose you or us to legal liability.

**Legal Rights**  
We may disclose your Information where necessary for the purpose of exercising, establishing or defending our legal rights. For example, we may review your gameplay, communications, and other account information in order to investigate allegations of cheating, hacking or any other breach or alleged breach of any applicable Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy and disclose your personal information, including communications, to our legal advisors, consultants and law enforcement or other government officials.

**Vital interests**  
We may disclose your Information with third parties where we believe this is necessary to protect the vital interests of any person. For example, we may disclose Information relating to an online account if we in good faith believe the user of that account is using it in ways that are harmful to others (e.g. making inappropriate contact with minors).

**Sale of our business or assets**  
Separately, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, Activision's customer information including Information and communications may be transferred to our successor or assign.

Back to top

**7\. Security**  
Activision takes a range of security measures designed to help protect your Information. However, complete online and offline security can never be guaranteed, so you should always take care when sharing your information online.

Click here for details Hide details

Activision takes a range of security measures designed to protect your personal information and keep it confidential (unless it is non-confidential by nature, for example, publicly-available information like user generated content, leaderboard rankings, and scores, etc.). We also take steps to ensure that the personal information collected is protected from misuse and alteration. In addition, we request vendors who process personal information on our behalf to themselves take a range of security measures designed to help protect your personal information. However, the Internet by its nature is not a secure environment and the nature of security risks is constantly evolving, as are the technical and organizational industry standards relating to management of those risks. The complete security of any personal information collected, stored or used by us or our vendors cannot therefore be guaranteed.

Back to top

If for any reason you wish to view, correct, update or delete personal information collected about you, simply access your Activision account through [ https://www.activision.com/](https://www.activision.com/) or other product or service as applicable and edit/delete your personal information. You will need your password to access your personal account. You may also send us an email asking us to delete your account at [removeaccount@activision.com](mailto:removeaccount@activision.com).

If you have any questions about the Information we process about you, or if you wish to view, update or delete your personal information, you can send your request to [privacy@activision.com](mailto:privacy@activision.com). Alternatively, US, Canada or Mexico residents may write to us at: Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405 USA, ATTN: Privacy Team/Privacy Policy; and users living in any other country may write to: Activision Blizzard UK Limited, Ditton Park, Riding Court Road, SLOUGH, Berks, SL3 9LL, UK,, ATTN: International Legal, Privacy. We will be happy to review, update or remove Information as appropriate.

Residual copies of Information that has been deleted from your account may remain in our backup systems for approximately one month. We may still retain your information to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, or comply with legal requirements; in this case, your personal information will be blocked from use for any other purpose.

Back to top

**9\. Contacting Us**  
If you reside in the United States, Canada or Mexico, this Privacy Policy applies between you and Activision Publishing Inc. If you reside in any other country, this Privacy Policy applies between you and Activision Blizzard UK Ltd. Activision Blizzard UK Limited is registered as data controller with the UK Information Commissioner's Office with registration number Z1095341.

Visitors from the US, Canada or Mexico can send us an email at [privacy@activision.com](mailto:privacy@activision.com), or write to us at: Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405, ATTN: Privacy Team/Privacy Policy, or call Privacy Team/Privacy Policy, ph. +1 310 255 2000.

Visitors from another country can send us an email at [privacy@activision.com](mailto:privacy@activision.com), or write to us at: Activision Blizzard UK Limited of Ditton Park, Riding Court Road, SLOUGH, Berks, SL3 9LL, UK.

You may also contact ESRB Privacy Certified if you have a question or complaint that has not been resolved to your satisfaction. Please see the  **ESRB Privacy Certified Program**  section at the top of this Privacy Policy for further details.

**10\. Important Notice**  
For privacy related information applicable to users who are California residents or based outside the US please see below.

Please note your use of this Activision website, product or service is also subject to the terms of the Activision End User License Agreement available [here](https://support.activision.com/license) and Terms of Use available here.

**11\. California Privacy Rights**  
Since 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not share our customer's personal information with unaffiliated third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. For inquiries regarding our disclosure policy, please send us an email to [privacy@activision.com](mailto:websitedisclosurepolicy@activision.com), or write us at: Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405 USA, ATTN: Privacy Team/Privacy Policy. We will be happy to honor your request.

**California Privacy Rights for Minor Users**  
Since January 1, 2015, California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits you, if you are a California resident under the age of 18, to view, correct, or delete information provided by you or publicly posted by you, by simply accessing your Activision account through <https://www.activision.com/> or other product or service as applicable and editing/deleting your Information. You will need your password to access your personal account. You may also send us an email asking us to delete certain posted content at [privacy@activision.com](mailto:privacy@activision.com). In the alternative, you may write to us at Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405 USA, ATTN: Privacy Team/Privacy Policy.

We will be happy to review, update or remove information and/or content as appropriate. Residual copies of information and/or content that have been deleted from your account and/or the Properties may remain in our backup systems for up to 30 days. We may still retain your information to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, or comply with legal requirements; in this case, your personal information will be blocked from use for any other purpose.

Back to top

**12\. Disclosure to Users Outside the US**  
In addition, if you are a visitor to our websites or other online products and services from outside the U.S., the personal information you provide may be collected, processed and stored directly on, or transferred to, servers in the United States or other countries where Activision group companies or vendors maintain facilities or business operations.

Information collected with the European Economic Area and Switzerland may be transferred to the United States. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you agree such international transfers of your Information.

No matter where the Information is located, Activision takes all commercially reasonable measures to safeguard your privacy rights in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the collection, processing, storage and transfer of your information, please do not provide your information when requested and stop using our websites and other online products and services.

Back to top

**13\. Cookie Policy**  
Activision uses Cookies and/or similar technologies on the Properties. A "Cookie" is a small bit of record-keeping information that many websites and other online products and services often store on a user's computer or device in order to identify it and associate activity with it.

When visiting the Properties you have options to enable or disallow Cookies. We use Cookies to optimize your visit, make your browsing and user experience as effective as possible, and let you know about offers and features that we think will interest you. This means that if you disallow cookies, your use of the Properties may be impaired.

Depending on the Property you are using, and the country you are based in, Cookies may be set on your computer or device by either:

  * Activision - to recognize and associate activity with your computer or device when it visits a Property. Activision cookies cannot be used to recognize or associate activity with your computer or device when it visits other, third party websites or online properties.
  * Third Parties - to enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through our Properties or other online properties (e.g. advertising and analytics). The third parties that set these cookies may be able to recognize your computer or device both when it visits the Properties or other online properties that use the third party's features and functionality

Click here for details Hide details

**Types Of Cookies**  
There are four categories of Cookies that may be served through our Properties, described below. To see a list of the specific Cookies that may be served through our Properties, please see the Cookie List at the bottom of this Privacy Policy:

  * _Necessary Cookies_

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around websites or online properties and use their features, such as accessing secure areas of a website. Without these cookies, Activision cannot provide services you have asked for, like secure login areas.

  * _Performance (or Analytics) Cookies_

These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website or online property, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don't collect information about the actual identity (e.g., name) of a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. They are only used to improve how a website or other online property works. We generally contract with independent research and measurement companies, such as Google Analytics, to provide these services on our behalf and these third parties also have their own privacy policies.

  * _Functionality Cookies_

These cookies allow the website or online property to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personalized features. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customize. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video. The information these cookies collect may be anonymized and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.

  * _Advertising Cookies_

These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. They also help limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertising networks with the website or online property operator's permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organizations such as advertisers. Quite often advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organization. In certain countries Activision may partner with third party online advertising and analytics companies to tailor and deliver advertisements, products, services, and promotions on our Properties, as well as other online properties which we do not control. To help select the ads of greatest interest to you, these companies may use cookies, Flash technology, and similar technologies to collect and track information such as demographic data (e.g., gender, occupation, etc.), aggregated information, search keywords, geo-location and device-related data (for example, browser type, language, IP address, time/date) to select advertisements that are more relevant to your interests, to better personalize the experience for you and tailor advertisements. In some instances, third-parties may also use cookies or similar technologies to collect anonymized or device-related information about your visits to the Properties in order to provide third party advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.

To learn more about Advertising Cookies and your opt-out choices, visit the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) at [http://networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/) or [http://youronlinechoices.com](http://youronlinechoices.com/).

Activision may use and share anonymized or aggregated information obtained from cookies with third parties such as vendors or advertising partners. An example of the use of such information would be creating interest categories or segments based on region, gaming preferences, or a combination. We may also share personal and non-personal information obtained from cookies with third parties such as vendors or advertising networks in order to permit them to provide services on our behalf or to partner with us in selecting and serving advertisements for us or our advertising partners.

**Social Network Sites**

If you have signed in to a social networking site, such as Facebook, it may have set a cookie on your device which recognizes you when you view content on our websites and other online properties. These cookies allow you to share content across social media via the use of sharing settings. See your social networking site's terms of use and privacy policy for details. For additional details, please see the Social Media in the _Information We Collect And How We Use It_ and _Your Choices_ sections above.

**Do Not Track**

California Business and Professions Code Section 22575(b) (as amended effective January 1, 2014) permits our customers who are California residents to be informed as to how Activision responds to Web browser "Do Not Track" settings. As Do Not Track is a standard that is currently being developed, Activision does not take actions to respond to Do Not Track settings, and instead we adhere to the standards set out in this Privacy Policy.

**More Information**

If you would like to find out more about cookies you may find the following link useful:

If you would like to find out more about Do Not Track you may find the following link useful:

<http://www.allaboutdnt.com/>

**Managing Cookies & Do Not Track Options:** You can review your options to manage cookies by:

  * clicking on the opt out links provided in the Cookie List below
  * opening the "Help" menu on the browser menu bar. Most browsers will tell you how you can disable or delete cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.
  * visiting _<http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>_ and/or _[http://youronlinechoices.com](http://youronlinechoices.com/)_ for choices to opt out of advertising

If you reject all cookies, you may not be able to use certain features of our websites and other products and services (including sign in).

**Permission to Use Cookies**  
By using the Properties you agree to receive cookies unless you manage your cookie choices by one of the means set out above.

Please also note that the use of information obtained by third party providers listed in the Cookies List below through cookies placed by them is also subject to their own privacy policies. Information collected by cookies may be associated with your registration account or user profile.

**Flash cookies, web beacons, IP addresses**  
Adobe Flash Player is an application that allows sites to deploy dynamic web content. Adobe Flash and similar applications use technology to remember settings, preferences, and usage in ways that are similar to browser cookies, but are managed through a different interface than your web browser. You can access your Flash management tools from <http://www.adobe.com/> directly to manage your cookie settings. From time to time, we may use web beacons (or clear GIFs) on our Properties or include them in the email messages we send you. Web beacons (also known as "web bugs") are small strings of code that provide a method of delivering a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. We use web beacons for many purposes, including site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising and email auditing and reporting, and personalization. We also keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.

**Cookies List**  
The Properties may contain, but are not limited to, the following third party Performance (or Analytics) and Advertising cookies. Please follow the links below for details of the Privacy Policies and opt out choices offered by these third parties. Please also see the Cookie Policy above for further options available to manage cookies.

**Online Property**

| 

**Third Party Cookies**

| 

**Third Party Privacy Policies and Opt Out Choices**  
  
---|---|---  
  
**Websites**

| 

Add This

| 

  | 

Adobe Test & Target

| 

<http://www.adobe.com/privacy/analytics.html>

<http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html>  
  
  | 

Comscore

| 

<http://www.comscore.com/About_comScore/Privacy_Policy>

<http://www.sitestat.com/>  
  
  | 

Cross Pixel Media

| 

<http://datadesk.crsspxl.com/#/privacy-policy>

<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>  
  
  | 

Data Logix

| 

<https://www.datalogix.com/privacy/>  
  
  | 

Google Analytics

| 

<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>  
  
  | 

Sizmek

| 

<http://www.sizmek.com/about-us/privacy>  
  
  | 

Dstillery (formerly Media6 Degrees)

| 

<http://dstillery.com/privacy-policy/>  
  
  | 

ScoreCard Research

| 

[http://www.scorecardresearch.com/privacy.aspx?action=cookieTest&trackid=-1&sitegroup=20&siteid=10300&languageid=1](http://www.scorecardresearch.com/privacy.aspx?action=cookieTest&trackid=-1&sitegroup=20&siteid=10300&languageid=1)

<http://www.scorecardresearch.com/preferences.aspx?newlanguage=1>  
  
  | 

ShareThis

| 

<http://sharethis.com/privacy#sthash.aRj1rLCs.dpbs>  
  
  | 

Tribal Fusion

| 

<http://exponential.com/privacy/>

<http://exponential.com/ad-choices/>  
  
  | 

Videology

| 

<http://www.videologygroup.com/index.php/en/menu-privacy-policy.html>  
  
| 

Accuen

| 

<http://www.accuenmedia.com/privacy-policy/>  
  
| 

Kenshoo

| 

<http://kenshoo.com/privacy-policy/>  
  
| 

Doubleclick

| 

<http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>  
  
| 

Xaxis

| 

<http://www.xaxis.com/static/view/privacy-policy>  
  
| 

Google Adwords

| 

<https://www.google.com/intl/en-US/policies/privacy/>  
  
| 

Facebook Exchange

| 

<https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>  
  
**Apps for mobile phones and tablets**

| 

Swrve

| 

<http://swrve.com/privacy-policy/>  
  
  | 

Flurry

| 

<http://www.flurry.com/user-opt-out.html>

<https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/index.htm>  
  
  | 

Kochava

| 

<https://www.kochava.com/privacy-policy/>  
  
| 

Tubemogul

| 

<http://www.tubemogul.com/compliance/privacy-policy/>  
  
| 

Upsight

| 

<http://www.upsight.com/pricing/privacy-policy/>  
  
  | 

Adjust

| 

<https://www.adjust.com/imprint/>  
  
  | 

Fiksu

| 

<https://www.fiksu.com/privacy-policy>  
  
  | 

Tableau

| 

<http://www.tableau.com/privacy>  
  
  | 

Amazon Red Shift

| 

Back to top
